Waterfront Employers Association of the Pacific Coast and the ILWU Records 5317
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Waterfront Employers Association of the Pacific Coast and the ILWU Records
1934-1946
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Waterfront Employers Association of the Pacific Coast
International Longshoremen and Warehousemen's Union (ILWU)
5317
2 cubic feet
2 linear ft.
Records (documents).
Records concerning the dispute between the Waterfront Employees Association of the Pacific Coast and the International Longshoremen and Warehousemen's Union.
5596222
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, February 22, 2013
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 11, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Stevedores -- United States; Stevedores -- Labor unions -- United States; United States. National War Labor Board (1942-1945); Meyer, Arthur S. (Arthur Simon), 1880-1955; Waterfront Employers Association of the Pacific Coast.; International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union.
5596222
- Employer Association's Exhibit, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Union Exhibit, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Government Exhibit, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Correspondence with Lee G. Paul, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- West Coast Longshoremen Case-NWLB Report, Recommendation and Opinions, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Longshoremen's Matter-New York City, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- A.S. Meyer Correspondence, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Correspondence with Anne Lopation, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- NWLB West Coast Longshore Case Library, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Waterfront Employers, Pacific Coast-Longshore Fact Finding Board, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Employer Exhibits Book 2 AAA-GGG, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Employer Exhibits Book 2 AAA-GGG, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Union Exhibits-West Coast Longshore Case, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Union Case Exhibits-West Coast Longshore Case, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Employee's Exhibits Book 1 A-Z, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Employee's Exhibits Book 1 A-Z, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 7)